[
    {
        "ancillaryData": "0x616e63696c6c61727944617461486173683a313065333966393061383265633639373766626235316235396233666238343932306630313163666433363966323764313737386630306364376261363365332c6368696c64426c6f636b4e756d6265723a38323933363634372c6368696c644f7261636c653a616336303335336135343837336334343631303132313638323961366139386364626263336633642c6368696c645265717565737465723a326330333637613964623233316464656264383861393462346636343631613665343763353862312c6368696c64436861696e49643a313337",
        "timestamp": 1770989129,
        "question": "Set Handicap: Valentova (-1.5) vs Birrell (+1.5)",
        "answer": "P3"
    },
    {
        "ancillaryData": "0x616e63696c6c61727944617461486173683a643663393638393262373161663164623761366534636433306230323362636136333135613464353461313239383934623166366437343930373461333166362c6368696c64426c6f636b4e756d6265723a38323932393836322c6368696c644f7261636c653a616336303335336135343837336334343631303132313638323961366139386364626263336633642c6368696c645265717565737465723a326330333637613964623233316464656264383861393462346636343631613665343763353862312c6368696c64436861696e49643a313337",
        "timestamp": 1770972705,
        "question": "Will Israel strike Gaza on February 12, 2026?",
        "answer": "P2"
    },
    {
        "ancillaryData": "0x6f6f5265717565737465723a63313836666139313433353363343462326533336562653035663231383436663130343862656461",
        "timestamp": 1770933167,
        "question": "Across V2",
        "answer": "P1"
    },
    {
        "ancillaryData": "0x616e63696c6c61727944617461486173683a343064653663366433313062613062303530303333343563613462373432383636383535646263333633393666383764323432363738613961333538666130382c6368696c64426c6f636b4e756d6265723a38323839373836382c6368696c644f7261636c653a616336303335336135343837336334343631303132313638323961366139386364626263336633642c6368696c645265717565737465723a326330333637613964623233316464656264383861393462346636343631613665343763353862312c6368696c64436861696e49643a313337",
        "timestamp": 1770915601,
        "question": "Counter-Strike: Sinners vs fnatic (BO3) - IEM Atlanta: Global Qualifier Playoffs",
        "answer": "P4"
    },
    {
        "ancillaryData": "0x616e63696c6c61727944617461486173683a396333363364383735343234323361663566373163396630303533303765653432653238346434643261356538613437333031393333393464316134356339342c6368696c64426c6f636b4e756d6265723a38323839323238372c6368696c644f7261636c653a616336303335336135343837336334343631303132313638323961366139386364626263336633642c6368696c645265717565737465723a326330333637613964623233316464656264383861393462346636343631613665343763353862312c6368696c64436861696e49643a313337",
        "timestamp": 1770904573,
        "question": "Will Israel strike Gaza on February 10, 2026?",
        "answer": "P2"
    },
    {
        "ancillaryData": "0x616e63696c6c61727944617461486173683a396333363364383735343234323361663566373163396630303533303765653432653238346434643261356538613437333031393333393464316134356339342c6368696c64426c6f636b4e756d6265723a38323839313732342c6368696c644f7261636c653a616336303335336135343837336334343631303132313638323961366139386364626263336633642c6368696c645265717565737465723a326330333637613964623233316464656264383861393462346636343631613665343763353862312c6368696c64436861696e49643a313337",
        "timestamp": 1770903395,
        "question": "Will Israel strike Gaza on February 10, 2026?",
        "answer": "P2"
    },
    {
        "ancillaryData": "0x616e63696c6c61727944617461486173683a616165376136326561343135306133306136663633633935343563396632353538343563653163336230663936383335316662623162333766643333353364312c6368696c64426c6f636b4e756d6265723a38323837363935302c6368696c644f7261636c653a616336303335336135343837336334343631303132313638323961366139386364626263336633642c6368696c645265717565737465723a656533616665333437643563373433313730343165323631386334393533346461663838376332342c6368696c64436861696e49643a313337",
        "timestamp": 1770873549,
        "question": "Will Trump and Netanyahu handshake last less than 2 seconds by February 13, 2026?",
        "answer": "P4"
    },
    {
        "ancillaryData": "0x616e63696c6c61727944617461486173683a666233306434323237666362646331383166386337333161613830646637623538636361303132663539383061393434626633633833373737613930653435362c6368696c64426c6f636b4e756d6265723a38323837363933352c6368696c644f7261636c653a616336303335336135343837336334343631303132313638323961366139386364626263336633642c6368696c645265717565737465723a656533616665333437643563373433313730343165323631386334393533346461663838376332342c6368696c64436861696e49643a313337",
        "timestamp": 1770873243,
        "question": "Will Trump and Netanyahu handshake last 10–15 seconds by February 13, 2026?",
        "answer": "P4"
    },
    {
        "ancillaryData": "0x616e63696c6c61727944617461486173683a313637616239636235303834306539666664633831623864333138613161623865656463633135333738356531636564313766363732303532626165656439382c6368696c64426c6f636b4e756d6265723a38323837363932372c6368696c644f7261636c653a616336303335336135343837336334343631303132313638323961366139386364626263336633642c6368696c645265717565737465723a656533616665333437643563373433313730343165323631386334393533346461663838376332342c6368696c64436861696e49643a313337",
        "timestamp": 1770873663,
        "question": "Will Trump and Netanyahu handshake last 2–6 seconds by February 13, 2026?",
        "answer": "P4"
    },
    {
        "ancillaryData": "0x616e63696c6c61727944617461486173683a356232303733316264393131633431636134653939626539303539376362393833313761646363616635643664393231326432626365346630356166666336372c6368696c64426c6f636b4e756d6265723a38323837363838342c6368696c644f7261636c653a616336303335336135343837336334343631303132313638323961366139386364626263336633642c6368696c645265717565737465723a656533616665333437643563373433313730343165323631386334393533346461663838376332342c6368696c64436861696e49643a313337",
        "timestamp": 1770873211,
        "question": "Will Trump and Netanyahu handshake last 6–10 seconds by February 13, 2026?",
        "answer": "P4"
    },
    {
        "ancillaryData": "0x616e63696c6c61727944617461486173683a353936306433633438346361663437313030393330376438333766366431353533383335636539353836303433653466653731356134646663613366663334322c6368696c64426c6f636b4e756d6265723a38323837363835362c6368696c644f7261636c653a616336303335336135343837336334343631303132313638323961366139386364626263336633642c6368696c645265717565737465723a656533616665333437643563373433313730343165323631386334393533346461663838376332342c6368696c64436861696e49643a313337",
        "timestamp": 1770872439,
        "question": "Will Trump and Netanyahu only be photographed together by February 13, 2026?",
        "answer": "P4"
    },
    {
        "ancillaryData": "0x616e63696c6c61727944617461486173683a623633633132646236653135633330376235663035623330643733663432383838643030393333353932323433393730346166383966343362666634353137622c6368696c64426c6f636b4e756d6265723a38323837363334382c6368696c644f7261636c653a616336303335336135343837336334343631303132313638323961366139386364626263336633642c6368696c645265717565737465723a326330333637613964623233316464656264383861393462346636343631613665343763353862312c6368696c64436861696e49643a313337",
        "timestamp": 1770872471,
        "question": "Will Trump say \"Israel\" 13+ times during meeting with Netanyahu?",
        "answer": "P1"
    },
    {
        "ancillaryData": "0x616e63696c6c61727944617461486173683a643661386137653034663736303336643165623233306261613433383431393334656337356565636661333066346630313263386462636462393439336664652c6368696c64426c6f636b4e756d6265723a38323836383433372c6368696c644f7261636c653a616336303335336135343837336334343631303132313638323961366139386364626263336633642c6368696c645265717565737465723a326330333637613964623233316464656264383861393462346636343631613665343763353862312c6368696c64436861696e49643a313337",
        "timestamp": 1770856561,
        "question": "Bulls vs. Heat",
        "answer": "P2"
    },
    {
        "ancillaryData": "0x616e63696c6c61727944617461486173683a313336666432656564656463616639336635363066643531313637613235623333313233356363316231323639646564323430346464666430353736656230332c6368696c64426c6f636b4e756d6265723a38323836343738362c6368696c644f7261636c653a616336303335336135343837336334343631303132313638323961366139386364626263336633642c6368696c645265717565737465723a656533616665333437643563373433313730343165323631386334393533346461663838376332342c6368696c64436861696e49643a313337",
        "timestamp": 1770848387,
        "question": "Will SOLV Energy, Inc.'s market cap be less than $3.8B at market close on IPO day?",
        "answer": "P1"
    },
    {
        "ancillaryData": "0x616e63696c6c61727944617461486173683a666634313265353839613261623537356662653533303531623731666231663132653236393430653230376436326261623761666138376366313738656536642c6368696c64426c6f636b4e756d6265723a38323836343038362c6368696c644f7261636c653a616336303335336135343837336334343631303132313638323961366139386364626263336633642c6368696c645265717565737465723a656533616665333437643563373433313730343165323631386334393533346461663838376332342c6368696c64436861696e49643a313337",
        "timestamp": 1770847301,
        "question": "Will the 2026 Bad Bunny Super Bowl halftime show video get fewer than 50M views in its first 7 days?",
        "answer": "P4"
    },
    {
        "ancillaryData": "0x616e63696c6c61727944617461486173683a313336666432656564656463616639336635363066643531313637613235623333313233356363316231323639646564323430346464666430353736656230332c6368696c64426c6f636b4e756d6265723a38323836343033322c6368696c644f7261636c653a616336303335336135343837336334343631303132313638323961366139386364626263336633642c6368696c645265717565737465723a656533616665333437643563373433313730343165323631386334393533346461663838376332342c6368696c64436861696e49643a313337",
        "timestamp": 1770847033,
        "question": "Will SOLV Energy, Inc.'s market cap be less than $3.8B at market close on IPO day?",
        "answer": "P1"
    },
    {
        "ancillaryData": "0x616e63696c6c61727944617461486173683a633232326133646330613933303339376463653832353665333134326637323065653462373863663234653762313237373836353962633330613865366665302c6368696c64426c6f636b4e756d6265723a38323836343030302c6368696c644f7261636c653a616336303335336135343837336334343631303132313638323961366139386364626263336633642c6368696c645265717565737465723a656533616665333437643563373433313730343165323631386334393533346461663838376332342c6368696c64436861696e49643a313337",
        "timestamp": 1770847089,
        "question": "Will SOLV Energy, Inc.'s market cap be greater than $5.4B at market close on IPO day?",
        "answer": "P2"
    },
    {
        "ancillaryData": "0x616e63696c6c61727944617461486173683a633232326133646330613933303339376463653832353665333134326637323065653462373863663234653762313237373836353962633330613865366665302c6368696c64426c6f636b4e756d6265723a38323836333431372c6368696c644f7261636c653a616336303335336135343837336334343631303132313638323961366139386364626263336633642c6368696c645265717565737465723a656533616665333437643563373433313730343165323631386334393533346461663838376332342c6368696c64436861696e49643a313337",
        "timestamp": 1770845913,
        "question": "Will SOLV Energy, Inc.'s market cap be greater than $5.4B at market close on IPO day?",
        "answer": "P2"
    },
    {
        "ancillaryData": "0x616e63696c6c61727944617461486173683a626132613562343762336435353532303965353035643863306136633032396662636330363863353763343830633535656439316434623332353133353534312c6368696c64426c6f636b4e756d6265723a38323836313837322c6368696c644f7261636c653a616336303335336135343837336334343631303132313638323961366139386364626263336633642c6368696c645265717565737465723a326330333637613964623233316464656264383861393462346636343631613665343763353862312c6368696c64436861696e49643a313337",
        "timestamp": 1770843707,
        "question": "Bitcoin Up or Down - February 11, 3PM ET",
        "answer": "P1"
    }
]
